# Aditya Rajak

I am a Technology enthusiast and Web Developer with 4+ years of experience, who is excited about the intersection of technology in everyday life. Experience working in agile environments using various Front-end technologies and frameworks.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Infosys - Technology Analyst

From August 2019

As Technology Analyst I am responsible to take part in client calls, understand the various requirements, implement solutions, suggest work improvements, mentoring of junior resources for technical assistance, report the work status in timely manner.

# Cyber Infrastructure Pvt. Ltd. – Developer

From March 2016 - August 2019

As Developer I am responsible for handling projects individually. I communicate with clients directly. Understand their requirements, prepare project plans and requirements. I also have experience in working with team which were geographically separated in different time zones.

#### Devu.in — Web Developer

August 2015 - February 2016

As Web Developer my role was learn Industry coding standards. Complete task given by senior developers. Along with that due to my good coding skills and knowledge I got chance to work on live project.

#### **EDUCATION**

# Bansal Institute of Research & Technology, Bhopal— B.E.

Aug 2011 - May 2015

I have completed Bachelors of Engineering in Computer Science branch from this college.

Govt Excellence Higher Secondary School, Bhua Bichhiya (Dist. Mandla) — *H.Sc.* 

#### (+91) 9039878010

adityarajak9@gmail.com

Passport No. - N2009590

#### **SKILLS**

HTML, CSS.

Python, Django, Kivy, Web2py, Odoo, Numpy, Pandas.

Jupyter, Microsoft code editor. JavaScript, NodeJs, Bubble.is, Apache, MySQL, PSQL, Mongo DB.

SDN/NFV, SDWAN, Docker, Kubernetes, OpenStack.

# INTERESTS & ACHIEVEMENTS

#### Captain of U-19 Team -

Represented Jabalpur as a Captain of U-19 cricket team, organised by state govt.

Diploma – Diploma In

Computer Application & Programming (DCPA) from IGNOU, New Delhi, 2011.

#### **LANGUAGES**

Hindi, English

# Strength

Quick Learner, Self-Motivated

#### Hobbies

Playing Cricket, Eager to learn new programming Languages, Listening Music, Cooking. I have completed Higher Secondary from MP board from this school.

# Saraswati Shishu Mandir, Bhua Bichhiya(Dist. Mandla) — S.Sc.

1997 - 2009

I have completed Senior Secondary from MP board from this school.

#### **CERTIFICATIONS**

**Python -** A Beginner's guide to Python Programming Language — Udemy

**SDN/NFV** – Introduction to software defined networking and Network function virtualisation — Infosys

NFVI OpenStack - RedHAT certified OpensSack Delivery Specialist laaS (External) — Infosys

Django - Python & Django Full Stack Web Developer Bootcamp — Udemy

Odoo - Restaurant Management — Udemy

NodeJS - The MEAN Stack Guide — Udemy

**Being Agile Aware -** Overview of Agile approach to software development, flavours of Agile and DevOps practise to accelerate and sustain it. — Infosys

#### **PROJECTS**

### ONF SEBA - SDN, Python, Angular, Docker, Kubernetes, AWS Cloud.

- 1. SEBA: SDN-Enabled Broadband Access (SEBA) is an Exemplar Platform being built by the ONF and CORD community.
- 2. Installation and maintenance of SEBA-in-a-box, troubleshooting failures, testing of new code in SEBA-in-a-box.
- 3. Worked on UI development part of XOS GUI tool to transform SEBA UI to INFOSYS ISDA UI.
- 4. Used Gitlab for pushing the code and Docker Hub for pushing the image.

### Comcast TWAG - SDN, Python, RYU Controller, SPIDER, DHCP Server.

- 1. TWAG: is a prototype at the time of writing this, an attempt to use SDN & NFV to virtualise the Wifi Access Gateway and add 3GPP interfaces such as S2A/B and STA to convert xfinitywifi SSID as a trusted wifi network access for Xfinity Mobile.
- 2. DHCP Server (ISC-DHCP-Server) Installations.
- 3. Following OpenFlow Protocol.
- 4. Using OVS as a virtual switch in VM environments.
- 5. Created GRE Tunnel between two Mininets.

# Siphtor— Python 3.x, Django, Mysql, Machine Learning (Crab, k-means clustering), Open Calais, Scrapy.

'Siphtor', which is a news article related online website. The users' news feed is populating with news articles from the certain database based upon a score ranking of the most relevant documents. There are some features and description

about the functionality of this project which describes how we used Machine Learning approach to making the concept work as seamless user experience.

# Rataran — Python 2.x, Django 1.7, Mysql

Rataran is an online product which developed on the combination of Python and Django, which revolutionise the ordinary model of Asset Management by rewarding the best talents.

# ERP- Python 2.x, Odoo, Mysql

ERP is an online product which developed on one of the finest framework of Python i.e. Odoo, this software deals with transaction of products from branches to inventories and inventories to sub-inventories. Moto of this software is to track all the details of an enterprise regarding product exchange, product delivery & cost management.

# Saloon Management System — Python3.x, Mysql

It is a management system for salons. Users can choose from many saloons nearby their location and saloon owner can manage bookings of its employees. Basically this is a booking management system where user can schedule its booking with wide range of products.

# Charity Management System — Python3.x, Mysql, Braintree

This is a charity donation system which allows users to donate amount to specific charity. This system has user role management system. User can register themselves as business or charity before registering user had to choose from plans which this system has offering. We have integrated Braintree as payment gateway in this system.

### BTC Bet App — Node Js, Java, MongoDB

It is a Malaysia based betting system which deals in Bitcoins. Here we are crawling data from 10 different different websites and showing data in this app using Node Js as front end.

#### Bubble.is — JavaScript, HTML 5, REST APIs

Bubble lets us build and host web applications without having to write code or hire a team of engineers. I have design many web and native application in this platform. Below is the list of applications and plugins.

- 1. Living 3D (https://living3d.it/) :- In this application, we have solved the issue of showing 3D images in all the mobile and web Browsers without any error.
- 2. Pamperly (https://beauteewebsite.bubbleapps.io/version-test?debug=true) :- We have developed this beautiful theme application based on the beauty salon theme from the scratch.
- 3. Aventurista(https://aventurista.es/):- We have added the Stripe payment system with the multiple vendors features.

### **PLUGINS**

- 1. Image Marker:- https://forum.bubble.is/t/image-marker-plugin-to-mark-the-pin-points-of-your-images/37421
- Image 360:- https://bubble.is/plugin/aditya-360°-viewer-image-1521453221806x634354832628514800
   All Country Data:- https://bubble.is/plugin/all-country-data-1521813310666x368316118531047400
   Game of Numbers:- https://bubble.is/plugin/game-of-numbers-1545731868075x160267905197670400